Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Subjects, 1979-1994
  - Subseries A: Loft
    - Chemical Bank 1991, cuid26751 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Receipts 1990, misc., cuid26752 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Medical receipts 1990, cuid26753 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Chemical Bank 1990, cuid26754 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Con Edison 1990, cuid26755 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - NY Telephone 1990, cuid26756 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Receipts 1989, misc., cuid26757 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Medical receipts 1989, cuid26758 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Con Edison 1989, cuid26759 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - NY Telephone 1989, cuid26760 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Chemical Bank 1989, cuid26761 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Receipts 1988, misc., cuid26762 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Medical receipts 1988, cuid26763 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Manhattan Bank 1988, cuid26764 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Amalgamated Bank 1988, cuid26765 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Chemical Bank 1988, cuid26766 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Con Edison 1988, cuid26767 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - NY Telephone 1988, cuid26768 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Receipts-empty folders, undated; cuid26769 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Tax, undated; cuid26770 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Hujar, Peter-bills, undated; cuid26771 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Hujar, Peter-bills, undated; cuid26772 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Hujar, Peter-bills, undated; cuid26773 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Hujar, Peter-birth certificate, diploma, social security, etc., undated; cuid26774 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Hujar, Peter-c. v., undated; cuid26775 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Hujar, Peter-disability report, undated; cuid26776 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Hujar, Peter-home care plan, undated; cuid26777 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Hujar, Peter-medical, undated; cuid26778 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Hujar, Peter-model release forms, undated; cuid26779 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Hujar, Peter-obituary, undated; cuid26780 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Hujar, Peter-obituary, undated; cuid26781 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Hujar, Peter-obituary "Portrait in Life.", undated; cuid26782 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Hujar, Peter-receipts, undated; cuid26783 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Hujar, Peter-will, undated; cuid26784 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Subseries B: Legal Cases
    This subseries contains documentation pertaining to the Reverend Wildmon trial and NEA legal battles.
    - Auto accident summons, undated; cuid26785 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Legal misc., undated; cuid26786 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Legal misc. -will of Keith Davis, undated; cuid26787 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Legal misc. -guidelines for will, undated; cuid26788 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - NEA-Artists Space, undated; cuid26789 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - NEA-"Culture Wars" by Ed Richard Bolton, undated; cuid26790 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - NEA-"Left & Right ..." by David Levi Strauss, undated; cuid26791 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - NEA-"NEA Restores $10,000 Grant ... " by Karen Lipson (NY Newsday), undated; cuid26792 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - NEA-Illinois State University controversy articles/clippings, undated; cuid26793 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - NEA-Illinois correspondence re: attacks on retrospective by NEA, undated; cuid26794 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - NEA-Illinois correspondence re: "Tongues of Flame" exhibit, undated; cuid26795 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - NEA-Ollie North file, undated; cuid26796 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - NEA-Postcards from America excerpt, undated; cuid26797 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - NEA-Proof (Artist's Equity) "Paint or Politics", undated; cuid26798 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - NEA/AFA case-reviews, undated; cuid26799 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Wildmon-AFA fax, undated; cuid26800 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Wildmon-AFA fax, undated; cuid26801 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Wildmon-AFA flyer, undated; cuid26802 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Wildmon-AFA letter about Wojnarowicz, undated; cuid26803 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Wildmon-AFA letter requesting money, undated; cuid26804 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Wildmon-AFA memo, undated; cuid26805 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Wildmon/NEA-articles and clippings, undated; cuid26806 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Wildmon-article in Art in America, "War on Culture", undated; cuid26807 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Wildmon-article in NY Times Magazine, "Reverend Wildmon's ..." (Sept. 2, 1990), cuid26808 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Wildmon case, undated; cuid26809 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Wildmon case-envelope and phone log, undated; cuid26810 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Wildmon-complaint/nature of claim, undated; cuid26811 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Wildmon/AFA court materials, undated; cuid26812 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Wildmon-court transcripts, undated; cuid26813 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Wildmon-flyer denouncing Wojnarowicz, undated; cuid26814 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Wildmon-law memo draft (2 versions), undated; cuid26815 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - legal letter to Wildmon, undated; cuid26816 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Wildmon-legal brief notes, undated; cuid26817 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Wildmon-legal briefing notes (final version), undated; cuid26818 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Wildmon-memorandum of law, undated; cuid26819 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Wildmon-misc. flyers and memo, undated; cuid26820 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Wildmon-notes, undated; cuid26821 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Wildmon-notes, undated; cuid26822 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - notes on Wildmon mailing, undated; cuid26823 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - notes on Wildmon mailing, undated; cuid26824 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - Wildmon-notice of appeal, undated; cuid26825 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - Wildmon-People for the American Way, undated; cuid26826 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - Wildmon-plaintiff's trial memo, undated; cuid26827 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - Wildmon-post-trial brief, undated; cuid26828 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - Wildmon-post-trial brief on libel, undated; cuid26829 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - Wildmon-post-trial memo, undated; cuid26830 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - Wildmon-practice cross-examination for Wojnarowicz, undated; cuid26831 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Wildmon-request for documents, undated; cuid26832 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - Wildmon-trial memo, undated; cuid26833 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Wildmon-Wojnarowicz's affidavit, undated; cuid26834 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Wildmon-Wojnarowicz's affidavit, undated; cuid26835 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Wildmon-Wojnarowicz's deposition, undated; cuid26836 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - Wildmon-AFA check for $1. 0, undated; cuid26837 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Subseries C: Announcements
    This subseries includes flyers, posters, and promotional material concerning political activism, Wojnarowicz's rock'n'roll band 3 Teens Kill 4, art exhibitions, and various cultural and social events.
    - Activist/political flyers, undated; cuid26838 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26839 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26840 (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26841 (Box 15, Folder 109)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26842 (Box 15, Folder 110)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26843 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26844 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26845 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26846 (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26847 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26848 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - Announcements, undated; cuid26849 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - Announcements - Art in America June, 1994, cuid26850 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Announcements - Art in America February, 1989, cuid26851 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Announcements - Flyer for '3 Teens Kill 4', undated; cuid26852 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - '3 Teens Kill 4' Flyers/Posters, undated; cuid26853 (Box 15, Folder 120A.)
    - The Poetry Project, undated; cuid26854 (Box 15, Folder 120B.)
    - Program - Brighton Festival, undated; cuid26855 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Subseries D: General Subjects
    This subseries includes material on PPOW gallery, Dennis Cooper, and Tom Rauffenbart.
    - Cooper, Dennis, undated; cuid26856 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Exit Art-Mailing List, undated; cuid26857 (Box 15, Folder 122A.)
    - Festival of Arts Cruise, undated; cuid26858 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - L'Ecuyer, Gerald, undated; cuid26859 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - PPOW-Announcements, undated; cuid26860 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - PPOW-Bio and CV, undated; cuid26861 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - PPOW-Business, undated; cuid26862 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - PPOW-Reviews, undated; cuid26863 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Production Materials-Brush Fires in the Social Landscape, undated; cuid26864 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - Rauffenbart, Tom-instructions for medication, undated; cuid26865 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Rauffenbart, Tom-medical card, undated; cuid26866 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - Rauffenbart, Tom-rPsumP, undated; cuid26867 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Target City Hall materials --- Aids activism, undated; cuid26868 (Box 15, Folder 132A.)
- Series VIII: Audio, 1977-1992
  Scope and Content
  Series VIII contains both complete audio works and audio source materials. Letters and number sequences at the end of each description refer to the original box in which the work was found. Additional audio works are found in Accretions 2001.
  Subseries A: Access Copies is open to researchers. For all other material please consult a Fales Archivist. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
  This series is arranged into eight subseries: Subseries A: Access Copies; Subseries B: Primary Audio Works; Subseries C: Sound Materials; Subseries D: Original Music/ Wojnarowicz & Others; Subseries E: Phone Message Tapes; Subseries F: Commercial Audiotapes; Subseries G: Dubbed Audiotapes; and Subseries H: Unidentified/blank tapes.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Contains access copies for original material found in Series VIII: Subseries B, C, D, and E
    - Mexico Soundtrack, Unknown; ID: 092.0463 (Box 200, Cd 092.0463)
      Content description: Audio recording believed to correspond with Super 8mm film "A Fire in My Belly, a Work in Progress"
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirement note
      Format: CD
      Duration: 00:30:17
      Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette
      Source: 092.0361
    - 1988 Journal, Wojnarowicz, Nov., Dec. #1 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0465 (Box 200, Cd 092.0465)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz talks about living at the deceased Peter Hujar's apartment, his feelings regarding his own mortality, and frustrations with the art world among other things.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Duration: 00:47:08
      Source: 092.0218
    - 1988 Journal, Wojnarowicz, Nov., Dec. #1 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0467 (Box 200, Cd 092.0467)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz speaks about his dreams, promiscuity, and fears about dying of AIDS among other things.
      Duration: 00:47:05
    - ACT UP Demonstration, June 1989, ID: 092.0469 (Box 200, Cd 092.0469)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz records the ACT-UP demonstrations on June 1989.
      Duration: 00:13:27
      Source: 092.0219
    - "Affair" Tape Journal 3 / 1981 (Side 1 and 2), March 1981; ID: 092.0471 (Box 200, Cd 092.0471)
      Content description:
      [1]-- Wojnarowicz speaks about the social difficulties he has relating to dating among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz speaks about his creative process, self-doubt, and negative art critiques among other things.
      Duration:[1]--00:30:59 [2]--00:28:29
      Source: 090.0220
    - AIDS Vaccines / Gary Null Show / WBAI-5/18/90, NYC (Part 1 of 2), May 18th, 1990; ID: 092.0473 (Box 200, Cd 092.0473)
      Content description: Recording of the Gary Null Snow on WBAI-5/18/1990. The show's topic is about AIDS vaccines.
      Duration: 00:42:36
      Source: 092.0221
    - AIDS Vaccines / Gary Null Show / WBAI - 5/18/90, NYC (Part 2 of 2), May 18th, 1990; ID: 092.0475 (Box 200, Cd 092.0475)
      Content description: Part 2 of a recording Wojnarowicz made of the Gary Null Snow on WBAI-5/18/1990. The show's topic is about AIDS vaccines.
      Duration: 00:46:23
    - American Dreamtime: NYC, 1984, ID: 092.0477 (Box 200, Cd 092.0477)
      Content description: Experimental recording by Wojnarowicz and Doug Bressler, called "American Dreamtime." New York City, 1984.
      Duration: 00:05:37
      Source: 092.0222
    - Cross Country / Great Dreams- 1989, ID: 092.0479 (Box 200, Cd 092.0479)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz's audio recordings, "Cross County/Great Dreams" documents a road trip he took in 1989. He talks about his feelings regarding the death of Peter Hujar among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz continues this recording in Arkansas. He talks about a dream he had and observations he's made while driving among other things.
      Duration: [1]--00:15:12 [2]--00:29:16
      Source: 092.0224
    - Cross Country / Great Dreams- 1989, ID: 092.0481 (Box 200, Cd 092.0481)
      [1]-- Wojnarowicz continues this series, "Cross Country/Great Dreams" in Alboroque, New Mexico. He talks about a dream he had of Peter Hujar among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz is now driving towards San Diego, California. He makes general observations about the places he's traveling through and records a visit he took to the park, Sea World.
      Duration: [1]--00:31:12 [2]--00:30:53
      Source: 092.0225
    - Cross Country / Great Dreams- 1989, ID: 092.0483 (Box 200, Cd 092.0483)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz continues his "Cross Country/Great Dreams" recordings on February 27th. He talks about his fears of dying and observations about New York City as compared to other US cities among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz documents his thoughts on the restrictions of living with AIDS coupled with his human desires among other things.
      Duration: [1]--00:30:52 [2]--00:30:04
      Source: 092.0226
    - David Wojnarowicz Interviewed by Keith Davis - Part 1 of 3 David (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0485 (Box 200, Cd 092.0485)
      Content description: A recording documenting an interview Keith Davis had with Wojnarowicz.
      Duration: 00:46:51
      Source: 092.0227
    - David Wojnarowicz Interviewed by Keith Davis - Part 2 of 3, ID: 092.0487 (Box 200, Cd 092.0487)
      Content description: Part 2 of a recording documenting an interview Keith Davis had with Wojnarowicz.
      Duration: 00:46:03
    - David Wojnarowicz Interviewed by Keith Davis - Part 3 of 3, ID: 092.0491 (Box 200, Cd 092.0491)
      Content description: Tracks [1] and [2] document an interview Keith Davis had with Wojnarowicz.
      Duration: [1]--00:46:56 [2]--00:33:11
      Source: 092.0230
    - David Queer Song, ID: 092.0489 (Box 200, Cd 092.0489)
      Content description: A recording of Wojnarowicz's "David Queer Song."
      Duration: 00:07:41
      Source: 092.0229
    - David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer - Part 1, ID: 092.0493 (Box 200, Cd 092.0493)
      Content description: Tracks [1] and [2] document a discussion between Wojnarowicz and Sylvere Lotringer. February 1991.
      Duration: [1]--00:33:44 [2]--00:30:33
      Source: 092.0232
    - David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer - Part 2, ID: 092.0495 (Box 200, Cd 092.0495)
      Duration: [1]--00:30:37 [2]--00:30:38
      Source: 092.0233
    - David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer - Part 3, ID: 092.0497 (Box 200, Cd 092.0497)
      Duration: [1]--00:12:20 [2]--00:06:11
      Source: 092.0234
    - "Affair" Tape Journal 3/81 - Side 3 and 4 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0502 (Box 200, Cd 092.0502)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz discusses a relationship he had when he was 26 among other things.
      [2]--Track 2 is a continuation of the discussion on Track 1.
      Duration: [1]--00:27:14 [2]--00:22:11
      Source: 092.0235
    - DesireTape (Last Version), ID: 092.0504 (Box 200, Cd 092.0504)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz talks about his difficulties dating and connecting to other men among other things. (Contains duplicate material found on 092.0471 - "Affair" Tape Journal.)
      [2]--Professinally mixed recording with overlapping vocals.
      Duration: [1]--00:12:19 [2]--00:16:54
      Source: 092.0236
    - Doug/David/Storefront/Do Not Tape Over This Side, ID: 092.0506 (Box 200, Cd 092.0506)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz records noise outside of a storefront and a experimental music recording.
      [2]--Music recording.
      Duration: [1]--00:24:20 [2]--00:31:22
      Source: 092.0237
    - Ending Loneliness Pt. 1 and 2 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0508 (Box 200, Cd 092.0508)
      Content description: A recording of a self-help workshop called "Ending Lonliness."
      Duration: 00:45:30
      Source: 092.0238
    - Ending Loneliness Pt. 1 and 2 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0510 (Box 200, Cd 092.0510)
      Content description: A recording of a self-help workshop titled "Ending Lonliness."
      Duration: 00:43:02
      Source:092.0238
    - Hujar Interview, Tape 1 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0512 (Box 200, Cd 092.0512)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz interviews photographer Peter Hujar. Hujar talkes about photography in the 1950's among other things.
      Duration: 00:47:11
      Source:092.0239
    - Hujar Interview, Tape 1 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0514 (Box 200, Cd 092.0514)
      Content description: A continuation of an interview with Wojnarowicz and photographer Peter Hujar. Wojnarowicz discusses Hujar's work in the context of contemporary photography among other things.
      Duration: 00:46:58
      Source: 092.0239
    - Interview: Mary Hayslip re: Montanna's Death 4/9/90/ Phil: Health Stuff/Richard Last Tape (Part 1 of 2), April 9, 1990; ID: 092.0516 (Box 200, Cd 092.0516)
      Content description: Mary Hayslip and Wojnarowicz discuss the death of Montanna among other things. They refer to him as "Monty" on the recording.
      Duration: 00:42:34
      Source: 092.0240
    - Interview: Mary Hayslip re: Montanna's Death 4/9/90/ Phil: Health Stuff/Richard Last Tape (Part 2 of 2), April 9, 1990; ID: 092.0518 (Box 200, Cd 092.0518)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz and Paul discuss the assisted death of an unnamed person who was dying from AIDS and the AIDS related health problems that Paul was experiencing among other things. Richard Kern talks about recovering from addiction among other things.
      Duration: 00:45:50
    - Interview With Ruth Hirschman- 7/23/90 (Parts 1 and 2), July 23, 1990; ID: 092.0520 (Box 200, Cd 092.0520)
      Content description: Ruth Hirschman interviews Wojnarowicz on the verge of his upcoming show at the Santa Monica Museum. They discuss Wojnarowicz's legal action against Donald Wildmon from the American Family Association and censorship in the art world among other things.
      Duration: 00:24:28
      Source:092.0241
    - [1]-- Arts/LA Radio Program: Tongues of Flame-8/13/90 [2]-- Edit of Interview With Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90, July 23, 1990; ID: 092.0522 (Box 201, Cd 092.0522)
      [1]--Recording of a radio show called Arts/LA. Show discusses the controversy surrounding Wojnarowicz on the precipise of his show, Tongues of Flame, at the Santa Monica Museum among other things.
      [2]--Additional recording depicting part of the Ruth Hirschman interview with Wojnarowicz.
      Duration: [1]--00:27:29 [2]--00:24:20
      Source: 092.0242
    - Interview with Susan Wyett/ Artists Space, NYC/ 60 min, ID: 092.0524 (Box 201, Cd 092.0524)
      Content description: National Public Radio (NPR) program discussing Jesse Helms and the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) among other things.
      Duration: 00:19:54
      Source: 092.0243
    - Jesse (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0526 (Box 201, Cd 092.0526)
      [1]--Recording of 4 different songs including a cover of "Unchained Melody."
      [2]--Recording of a song.
      Duration: [1]--00:16:15 [2]--00:02:26
      Source: 092.0244
    - John / David Conversation 12/31/1980 (Part 1 of 2), December 31, 1980; ID: 092.0528 (Box 201, Cd 092.0528)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz and John talk about masterbation among other things.
      Duration: 00:45:13
      Source:092.0245
    - John / David Conversation 12/31/1980 (Part 2 of 2), December 31, 1980; ID: 092.0530 (Box 201, Cd 092.0530)
      Content description: Part 2 of a recording where John and Wojnarowicz discuss their experiences looking for sex among other things.
      Duration: 00:45:05
      Source: 092.0245
    - Journal (Part 1 and 2), ID: 092.0532 (Box 201, Cd 092.0532)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz talks about his dreams among other things.
      [2]--Recording of Wojnarowicz singing and phone conversations including a interview about the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) debate over a exhibition catalogue among other things.
      Duration: [1]--00:31:11 [2]--00:31:06
      Source: 092.0246
    - Journal #2, 1988-89 (Part 1 of 2), 1988-1989; ID: 092.0534 (Box 201, Cd 092.0534)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz talks about his dreams, fears, and a sexual experience with a prostitute among other things.
      Source:092.0247
    - Journal #2, 1988-89 (Part 2 of 2), 1988-1989; ID: 092.0536 (Box 201, Cd 092.0536)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz talks about art in terms of money and class among other things.
      Duration: 00:47:07
      Source: 092.0247
    - Junk Journal, April 27-28, 1982, NYC (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0538 (Box 201, Cd 092.0538)
      [1]--Live introduction of the band 3 Teens Kill 4 and a recording of Wojnarowicz speaking about a time when he did "junk" among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz talks about being a young prostitute, his hopes, and dreams among other things.
      Duration: [1]--00:31:27 [2]--00:29:46
      Source: 092.0248
    - KCRW Radio Interview With Ruth Hirschman, ID: 092.0540 (Box 201, Cd 092.0540)
      Content description: Republican congressman, Ronald Packard speaks to radio host Ruth Hirshman about the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) grants and non-obscenity pledges among other things.
      Duration: 00:27:02
      Source: 092.0249
    - Ending Loneliness Part 3 and 4 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0542 (Box 201, Cd 092.0542)
      Tracks [1] and [2] are a continuation of a self-help workshop titled "Ending Lonliness."
      Duration: [1]--00:46:03 [2]--00:30:54
      Source: 092.0250
    - Performance Tape / Languages / Ming Ma Cantonese, ID: 092.0544 (Box 201, Cd 092.0544)
      Content description: Recording of man speaking in Cantonese.
      Duration: 00:02:02
      Source: 092.0261
    - Tape In Phone Machine "Kostabi" and "Phil Died" (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0546 (Box 200, Cd 092.0546)
      [1]--Answering maching recording of Mark Kostabi addressing some concerns to Wojnarowicz specifically regarding Wojnarowicz's recommendation that Kostabi's art work be taken out of a group show.
      [2]--Various answering maching recordings. The third recording is from Norman who called to inform Wojnarowicz that Phil died.
      Duration:
      [1]--00:08:13 [2]--00:04:29
      Source: 092.0263
    - Project Inform / 3-60 min, ID: 092.0548 (Box 201, Cd 092.0548)
      [1]--ACT UP representative introduces Martin Delaney and Joe Brewer of the San Francisco HIV positive advocacy group, Project Inform. This recording is the first in a series of town meetings that happened in New York City.
      [2]--Continuation of the Project Inform meeting. They're addressing holistic therapies as HIV treatments among other things.
      [1]--00:31:09
      [2]--00:31:06
      Source: 092.0265
    - Project Inform / 3-60 min (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0550 (Box 201, Cd 092.0550)
      [1]--A continuation of the Project Inform meeting. The speaker talks about the differing opinons and rationale regarding HIV treatments, like AZT among other things.